{
    "id": "c7384e1de64e4636874f649123423be2",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I lent ……………………… my pen.",
            "description": "When the indirect object goes before the direct object, there is no preposition.",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "to her",
                "for her"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4f90d87287764e75912f48eb163a2019"
        },
        {
            "question": "The old man told ………………………… the whole story.",
            "description": "There is no preposition between tell and its objects.",
            "answers": [
                "us",
                "to us",
                "for us"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "21b4ae7d971048bfac03799f14c62034"
        },
        {
            "question": "Show ………………………. your hands.",
            "description": "When the indirect object goes before the direct object, there is no preposition.",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "to me",
                "for me"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4b1fb4cff10947479a791e6c029c61b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I lent my pen ………………………",
            "description": "When the direct object goes before the indirect object, we put a preposition between them.",
            "answers": [
                "my friend",
                "to my friend",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f0771cc73f6144f394cbea62f565a1ac"
        },
        {
            "question": "She made coffee ……………………….",
            "description": "When the direct object goes before the indirect object, we put a preposition between them.",
            "answers": [
                "us",
                "to us",
                "for us"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0cc573d96f28432a815f80390e2ac195"
        },
        {
            "question": "She washed the plates ………………………",
            "description": "Here the correct pattern is subject + verb + noun/pronoun + adjective. In this case, the adjective denotes a state that results from the action expressed by the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "clean",
                "cleanly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "45d1e90c229b44148feb9fc6240e4871"
        },
        {
            "question": "We found the trunk ………………………",
            "description": "Here the correct pattern is subject + verb + noun/pronoun + adjective. In this case, the adjective denotes a state that results from the action expressed by the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "empty",
                "emptily",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "403d16bf7fe54721bbf7ede5f98a399f"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have made the walls …………………….",
            "description": "Here the correct pattern is subject + verb + noun/pronoun + adjective. In this case, the adjective denotes a state that results from the action expressed by the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "dirty",
                "dirtily",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "79672d9a4cbb4a2bbe11c54b26a5822e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has finished ………………………",
            "description": "The verb finish is usually followed by an ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "talking",
                "to talk",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "184c476a748c436288c555133add47f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I suggest ……………………….. travel insurance.",
            "description": "Suggest cannot be followed by a to-infinitive. We use an ing form instead.",
            "answers": [
                "to buy",
                "buying",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f06e84c23bb8496cb41433d993f2e756"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must not miss ……………………… him.",
            "description": "After miss, we use an ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "to see",
                "seeing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f842b08a3f3e411fbbace9bb8fdb5fc1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I consider the plan …………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unwise",
                "unwisely",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "880c5fced0824883ab6329d29e044178"
        }
    ]
}